Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
- Media, 1906-2014
  - 2. Magnetic Tape, 1954-2002
    - Open-Reel Tape, 1954-1996
      - 1/4" Tape, 1954-1996
        - Listening Room - Theremin - Part II, 1974-09-13; tr-16571; Moog, Robert; W2XR (Box 22)
        - Clara Rockmore #3, Undated; tr-16569; Moog, Robert (Box 22)
          Produced by Robert Moog
        - Blues Current, side 1, Undated; tr-16459; Murtaugh, John (Box 13)
        - Blues Current, side 2, Undated; tr-16460; Murtaugh, John (Box 13)
        - Studio di Mujica Elettronica di Torino, 1966; tr-16565; Musto, Roberto; Vianello, Riccardo (Box 22)
          6" reel
        - Newson: The Composer Develops, 1966-03; tr-16432; Newson, George (Box 13)
        - Silent Spring, 1967-09-1967-10; tr-16454; Newson, George (Box 13)
          Urbana, Illinois
        - Chopin Nocturnes, 1956; tr-16106; Novaes, Guiomar; Phonotapes Inc. (Box 7)
        - Assignment #3 - 4 Different Pieces, 1983-07-23; tr-16447; Pitera, Doug (Box 13)
        - Timing Test Moog Demo, 1971-08-11; tr-16427; Pittera, Doug (Box 13)
        - Mutations I, 1969; tr-16463; Rissett, Jean-Claude; Group de Recherches Musicals (Box 13)
          Running time: 10 minutes, 30 seconds
          Rissett, Jean-Claude
          Marseille, France
        - Songes, 1979; tr-16464; Rissett, Jean-Claude; Group de Recherches Musicals (Box 13)
          Running time: 9 minutes, 10 seconds
        - Computer Suite from Little Boy, Undated; tr-16461; Rissett, Jean-Claude (Box 13)
        - Avalanche, 1991; tr-17378; Robinson, Dick; Atlanta Electronic Music Center (Box 22)
        - Clara Rockmore, Undated; tr-16693; Rockmore, Clara; Sony Music (Box 33)
        - New 209, 1974-11-10; tr-16440; Rockmore, Clara (Box 13)
        - Composition for Tape Recorder, Undated; tr-16455; Rollia, Robert L. (Box 13)
        - Il Giuoco, 1966-03-16; tr-16457; Rudin, Andrew (Box 13)
          Running time: 15 minutes, 28 seconds
        - Blue Tail Fly, Undated; tr-16418; Ruether, D. (Box 9)
        - Zoological Gardens, Undated; tr-16431; Rzewski (Box 13)
        - The World of Sound, 1974-02-26; tr-16557; Siday, Eric (Box 22)
        - Demonstrations to accompany ASA paper 3aMU8 "Synthesizing musical tones by summing successive read-outs of a stored impulse response" (plus clarinet tones), 1994-06-08; tr-17379; Slaymaker, Frank (Box 22)
        - Letter and paper accompanying tr-17379, 1996-02-11; Slaymaker, Frank (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - Stack, Undated; tr-16439; Stack, Randy (Box 9)
        - BD I, Undated; tr-16556; Stahl (Box 22)
        - BD III, Undated; tr-16551; Stahl (Box 22)
        - BD III, Undated; tr-16555; Stahl (Box 22)
        - AUD 1038, 1977-05-18; tr-16419; Styles, Mark (Box 9)
        - Watchers, Players and Lovers, 1967-02; tr-16436; Swickard, Ralph (Box 9)
        - Eric Thurman, Undated; tr-16434; Thurman, Eric (Box 13)
          Kansas City, Kansas
        - Pams material with electronic beds, Undated; tr-16486; Thurman, Eric (Box 9)
        - Afternoon of a Faun/ Night on the Bare Mountain, Undated; tr-16458; Tomita, Isao (Box 13)
        - Pictures from an Exhibition, Undated; tr-16456; Tomita, Isao (Box 13)
        - Pictures from an Exhibition, Side B, Undated; tr-16452; Tomita, Isao (Box 13)
        - Pictures from and Exhibition, Side A, Undated; tr-16462; Tomita, Isao (Box 13)
        - Pentagram, 1981; tr-16572; Ussachevsky, Vladimir (Box 22)
        - Paul Vastola, Undated; tr-16473; Vastola, Paul (Box 9)
        - 3 tracks mixed to 1/2 tracks, Undated; tr-16437; Villani, A. David (Box 9)
        - Assignment II, Moog workshop, 1983-07-15; tr-16446; Williams, Steve (Box 13)
        - Study No. 10, Undated; tr-16424; Zajda, Ed (Box 9)
          Ciccero, Illinois
        - Test Tape, Undated; tr-16451; Standard Tape Laboratory (Box 13)
        - 1 (Scotch RB-7 tape), Undated; tr-16428 (Box 9)
        - 2 (Scotch RB-7 tape), Undated; tr-16429 (Box 9)
        - A Poem in Cycles and Bells, 1954; tr-16577 (Box 22)
        - AUD1009, Undated; tr-16430 (Box 9)
        - Bob Moog, Undated; tr-16575 (Box 22)
        - Bratislaw Vitos - Bass Playing, 1973-10-26; tr-16416 (Box 9)
        - Chorded and single note selections, 1970-03-17; tr-16471 (Box 22)
        - D.C. al Fine, 2nd tape, 1971-06-19; tr-16469 (Box 9)
        - Dolby A301 stretched, Undated; tr-16441 (Box 13)
        - Doubling test tape, Undated; tr-16409 (Box 9)
        - Dumbek Bookache IV, Undated; tr-16448 (Box 13)
        - EMS - Vocoder 2000 Demo, Undated; tr-16560 (Box 22)
        - Fantasy in Space; Incantation; Sonic Contours, Undated; tr-16574 (Box 22)
        - Five Sounds - For Alarm Clock Exp, 1972-06-07; tr-16559 (Box 22)
        - Insect Fear, Different Fur Trading Co., Viera and Gleeson, Undated; tr-16476 (Box 9)
        - Jazz combo, Undated; tr-16558 (Box 22)
        - Martiuetta, Undated; tr-16467 (Box 22)
          4" reel
        - Moog demo, Undated; tr-16408 (Box 9)
        - Moog demo, Undated; tr-16453 (Box 13)
        - Northern H.S. student compositions, 1971-11-29; tr-16472 (Box 22)
        - Peabody: Line of Apogee lecture, 1981-04-28; tr-16404 (Box 22)
          "Peabody lecture on my films"
        - Polish Electronic Music (Vol. 2), Undated; tr-16420 (Box 9)
        - Records, Undated; tr-16552 (Box 22)
          Track list: Clara, Sob, Sonic Seasonings, Chris Swansen, Country Moog, Suzuki
        - Riegger Villa Ladies, Undated; tr-16444 (Box 13)
        - SEV2008, Undated; tr-16426 (Box 9)
        - Sounds of the Putney, Undated; tr-16477 (Box 9)
        - Straight Out, Undated; tr-16443 (Box 13)
        - The Provoked Wife, Undated; tr-16414 (Box 9)
        - The Sound of the Moog - Side 2, Undated; tr-16579 (Box 22)
        - To the Young, Undated; tr-16581 (Box 22)
        - Unlabeled BSF tape, Undated; tr-16485 (Box 18)
        - Unlabeled Scotch 60 reel, Undated; tr-16435 (Box 13)
        - Unlabeled Scotch Sound Recording Tape, Undated; tr-16483 (Box 22)
        - Wedding, Undated; tr-16482 (Box 22)
  - 3. Phonograph Records, 1906-2003
    - Vinyl, 1946-2003
      - 12" Vinyl, 1946-2001
        Arranged alphabetically by artist.
        - Highlights from Verdi's La Traviata, Undated; SR-26094; Albanese, Licia; Merrill, Robert; Peerce, Jan; RCA Victor (Box 19)
          LM 1115
        - !!Going Places!!, 1964; SR-25863; Alpert, Herb, and the Tijuana Brass; A and M Records (Box 3)
          SP 4112
        - Whipped Cream and Other Delights, 1965; SR-25862; Alpert, Herb, and the Tijuana Brass; A and M Records (Box 3)
          SP 4110
        - American Brass Music, 1969; SR-25864; American Brass Quintet, The; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71222
        - Music From Utopia, 1985; SR-26188-26189; Anderson, Laurie; Bognermayr, Hubert; Zuschrader, Harald; Doldinger, Klaus; Jones, Howard; Moog, Bob; Plank, Moebius; Plank; Neumeier; Netzle, Klaus; Palmer, Poli; Prunster, Klaus; Schoener, Eberhard; Schultze, Kristian; Thurow, Matthias; Atma, Tri; Warrior, Jade; Yello; Erdenklang (Box 45)
          6.28650
        - [Japanese title], 1974; SR-26076; Aoe, Mina; JVC (Box 12)
          SJV-711
        - Alfred Apaka's Greatest Hits, 1964; SR-26095; Apaka, Alfred; Capitol Records (Box 19)
          DT-2088
        - Alfred Apaka's Greatest Hits, 1964; SR-26096; Apaka, Alfred; Capitol Records (Box 19)
          T-2088
        - Aloha, Apaka!, 1961; SR-26099; Apaka, Alfred; Decca Records (Box 19)
          DL 74150
        - My Isle Of Golden Dreams, 1963; SR-26098; Apaka, Alfred; Decca Records (Box 19)
          DL 74418
        - The Hawaiian Wedding Song, 1964; SR-26097; Apaka, Alfred; Decca Records (Box 19)
          DL 74571
        - Columbia-Princeton Electronic Music Center, 1964; SR-25865; Arel, Bülent; El-Dabh, Halim; Ussachevsky, Vladimir; Babbitt, Milton; Davidovsky, Mario; Luening, Otto; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          MS 6566
        - Electronic Music, 1958; SR-25866; Badings, Henk; Raaijmakers, Dick; Epic (Box 3)
          BC 1118
        - Instant Production Music, Volume 17 - Suite for Six Players, 1980; SR-26158; Barnett, Steve; University Of Wisconsin-Extension (Box 44)
          E-657A
        - Moog España, 1969; SR-26177; Bass, Sid; RCA Records (Box 44)
          LSP-4195
        - The In Sound From Way Out!, 1996; SR-26192; Beastie Boys; Grand Royal (Box 45)
          GR 013
        - Perchance to Dream, 1975; SR-25867; Beaver, Paul; Rapture Recordings (Box 3)
          11111
        - Live, 1977; SR-26206; Beck, Jeff; Jan Hammer Group; Epic Records (Box 45)
          X698
        - Africa Shona Mbira Music, 1977; SR-25868; Berliner, Paul; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-72077
        - Conducts for Young People, 1963; SR-25869; Bernstein, Leonard; New York Philharmonic; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          MS 6441
        - España, 1965; SR-25872; Bernstein, Leonard; New York Philharmonic; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          MS 6786
        - Saint-Saens: The Carnival of the Animals, 1962; SR-25870; Bernstein, Leonard; New York Philharmonic; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          MS 6368
        - Schubert: Unfinished Symphony; Mendelssohn: Italian Symphony, 1967; SR-25871; Bernstein, Leonard; New York Philharmonic; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          MS 7057
        - Synthi and the Composer, 1971; SR-25873; Birtwistle, Harrison; Zinovieff, Pete; Cary, Tristram; Derbyshire, Delia; Whitman, George; Simpson, Dudley; Clarke, Malcom; Vorhaus, David; Hodgson, Brian; Electronic Music Studios (Box 3)
        - Aniara: An Epic of Space Flight in 2038 A.D., 1960; SR-25874; Blomdahl, Karl-Birger; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          M2S 902
        - Passage, 1972; SR-25875; Bloodrock; Capitol Records (Box 3)
          SW-11109
        - Savannah Rhythms (Music Of Upper Volta), 1981; SR-26077; Bobo-Dyula tribe; Northern Samo Tribe; Groupe Instrumental Du Renouveau De La Jeuness Kassena De Po Et Tieble A Ouagadougou; Mossi Koranic Students; Fulani Ensemble; Mossi Tribe; Bwaba (Bobo-Oule) Tribe; Bissa Musicians; Nonesuch Records (Box 12)
          H-72087
        - Bessinung, 1981; SR-26264; Bognermayr, Hubert; Zuschrader, Harald; Elektronisches Försterhaus (Box 46)
          120.486
        - BergPredigt, 1983; SR-26265; Bognermayr, Hubert; Zuschrader, Harald; Erdenklang (Box 46)
          6.25590 AP
        - 2001 - A Space Odyssey - Music From The Motion Picture Soundtrack, 1971; SR-26139; Bohm, Karl; Berlin Philharmonic Orchestra; Travis, Francis; Bavarian Radio Orchestra; Gottwald, Clytus; Stuttgart Schola Cantorum; Von Karajan, Hervert; Rozhdestvensky, Gennadi; Leningrad Philharmonic Orchestra; Bour, Ernest; Sudwestfunk Orchestra; MGM Records (Box 44)
          S1E-13 ST X
        - Piano Music by George Gershwin, 1973; SR-25876; Bolcom, William; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71284
        - New Music For Organ, 1971; SR-25877; Bolcom, William; Albright, William; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71260
        - The Golden Age At The Metropolitan, 1951; SR-26100; Bori, Lucrezia; Puccini, Giacomo; Calve, Emma; Bizet, Georges; Caruso, Enrico; Verdi, Giuseppe; Farrar, Geraldine; Galli-Curci, Amelita; Journet, Marcel; Charpentier, Gustave; Meyerbeer, Giacomo; Ponselle, Rosa; Schipa, Tito; Tetrazzini, Luisa; Chaliapin, Feodor; Rethberg, Elisabeth; Berli State Opera Orchestra; McCormack, John; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 19)
          LCT-1006
        - Premiere Performances By Boston Musica Viva, 1987; SR-26078; Boston Musica Viva; Crawford Seeger, Ruth; Mekeel, Joyce; Musgrave, Thea; Delos (Box 12)
          DEL 25405
        - Baroque Guitar, 1966; SR-25878; Bream, Julian; RCA Victor (Box 3)
          LSC-2878
        - Popular Classics For Spanish Guitar, 1964; SR-26101; Bream, Julian; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 19)
          LSC-2606
        - La Guitarra Que Llora, Undated; SR-26102; Bribiesca, Antonio; Columbia Records (Box 19)
          EX-5034
        - Quartet In F Major / Quartet In G Minor, Opus 10, 1958; SR-25879; Budapest String Quartet, The; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          ML 5245
        - On Stage in Puerto Rico and in the Studio, 1972; SR-25880; Cactus; ATCO Records (Box 3)
          SD 7011
        - Electronic Music, 1967; Cage, John; Berio, Luciano; Mimaroglu, Ilhan; Turnabout; Missing vinyl; sleeve only. (Box 46)
          TV 34046S
        - Digital Moonscapes, 1984; SR-26263; Carlos, Wendy; CBS Records (Box 46)
          M 39340
        - The Well-Tempered Synthesizer, 1969; SR-26201; Carlos, Wendy; Columbia Records (Box 45)
          MS 7286
        - Sonic Seasonings, Disc 1, 1972; SR-25881; Carlos, Wendy (Box 3)
          Test pressing
        - Sonic Seasonings, Disc 2, 1972; SR-25882; Carlos, Wendy (Box 3)
        - The Well-Tempered Synthesizer, 1969; SR-26242; Carlos, Wendy (Box 46)
        - Sonata For Flute, Oboe, Cello & Harpsichord / Sonata For Cello & Piano, 1969; SR-25884; Carter, Elliott; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71234
        - String Quartets Nos. 1 & 2, 1970; SR-25885; Carter, Elliott; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71249
        - Spectrum, 1973; SR-26153; Cobham, Billy; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 44)
          SD-7268
        - Dear Lonely Hearts, 1962; SR-25886; Cole, Nat King; Capitol Records (Box 3)
          T-1838
        - The Sound Of Christmas, 1966; SR-26103; Cole, Nat King; Shore, Dinah; Hollyridge Strings, The; Crosby, Bing; Stafford, Jo; Hollywood Bowl Symphony Orchestra, The; Korean Orphan Choir, The; Ford, Tennessee Ernie; Waring, Fred, and the Pennsylvanians; Martino, Al; Capitol Records (Box 19)
          SL-6515
        - TellusTools, 2001; SR-25887; Collins, Nicolas; Lawler, Louise; Jackson, Isaac; Smith, Kiki; Tomlinson, Alan; Jones, Joe; Marclay, Christian; Knowles, Allison; Gen Ken; Jauniaux, Catherine; Mori, Ikue Linton, David; Whitehead, Gregory; League of Automatic Composers, The Lemaitre, Maurice; Lindhal, Jerry; Schellenbaum, Tim; Goldstein, Jack; Tellus (Box 3)
          TE-LP01
        - Hawaiian Album, 1967; SR-25890; Conniff, Ray; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          CL 2747
        - Somewhere My Love, 1966; SR-25889; Conniff, Ray; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          CL 2519
        - World of Hits, 1966; SR-25888; Conniff, Ray; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          CL 2500
        - Four Years Before 1984, 1980; SR-26137; Control Company; Telefunken (Box 44)
          6.24393 AP
        - Plugged In Pop, 1969; SR-26198; Copper Plated Integrated Circuit, The Plugged In Pop; Command Records (Box 45)
          945S
        - Planeten Sit-In, 1974; SR-25891; Cosmic Jokers, The; Metronome Records (Box 3)
          KM 58.013
        - Music from the Heart of Africa: Burundi, 1974; SR-25892; Coter, Giuseppe; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-72057
        - Ancient Voices Of Children, 1971; SR-25893; Crumb, George; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71255
        - Canti Illuminati, 1982; SR-26140; Curran, Alvin; Fore (Box 44)
          FORE 80/SEVEN
        - The Works, 1980; SR-26138; Curran, Alvin; Fore (Box 44)
          FORE 80/TWO
        - The Day After the Dawn, 1972; SR-26141; Dailey, Albert; Columbia Records (Box 44)
          KC 31278
        - The New Trumpet, 1972; SR-25894; Davies, Peter Maxwell; Dlugoszewski, Lucia; Hellerman, William; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71275
        - Russian Melodies, 1966; SR-25895; Decameron, Emil, and His Orchestra; Vanguard Recording Company (Box 3)
          SRV 201
        - Moog! Claude Denjean And The Moog Synthesizer, 1970; SR-26178; Denjean, Claude; London Records (Box 44)
          SP 44155
        - Exotic Moog, 1969; SR-20801; Denny, Martin; Liberty Records (Box 71)
          LST-7621
        - Prelude, 1972; SR-25896; Deodato; CTI Records (Box 3)
          CTI 6021
        - Omniphony 1, 1966; SR-25897; Dockstander, Tod; Reichert, James; Owl Records (Box 3)
          ORLP-11
        - Animus III/Synapse: Valentine, 1971; SR-25898; Druckman, Jacob; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71253
        - Spectrum: New American Music Volume III, Undated; SR-25899; Druckman, Jacob; Schwantner, Joseph; Harbison, John; Nonesuch Records (Box 3)
          H-71221
        - Drums are Dangerous, 1994; SR-20802; Drum Club; Butterfuly Records (Box 71)
          DCPRO 3; promo
        - We Could Have Danced All Night To, 1964; SR-25900; Duckin, Peter, His Piano and Orchestra; Decca Records (Box 3)
          DL 74436
        - Newborn Light, 1974; SR-25901; Dudziak, Ursula; CBS, Inc. (Box 3)
          KC 32902
        - Faces in Reflection, 1974; SR-25902; Duke, George; MPS Records (Box 3)
          MC 22018
        - Danton and Robespierre, 1980; SR-25903-25904, 26036; Eaton, John; Baldner, Thomas; Indiana University Opera Theater; CRI Records (Box 3)
          IUS 421
        - College Jazz: Modern, 1955; SR-26037; Eaton, Johnny, and his Princetonians; Columbia Records (Box 3)
          CL 737
        - Hawaii Calls: Hawaiian Strings: Favorite Instrumentals Of The Islands: Volume 3, 1959; SR-25905; Edwards, Webley; Capitol Records (Box 4)
          ST 1152
        - State-of-the-Art Electronic Devices, 1977; SR-25906; Electro-Harmonix Work Band; Electro-Harmonix (Box 4)
          ER 711
        - Moog Groove, 1969; SR-26175; Electronic Concept Orchestra; Limelight (Box 44)
          LS-86070
        - Moog Groove, 1969; SR-26176; Electronic Concept Orchestra; Limelight (Box 44)
        - Night Hawks, 1981; SR-25907; Emerson, Keith; Backstreet Records (Box 4)
          BSR-5196
        - Welcome Back My Friends To The Show That Never Ends ~ Ladies And Gentlemen, 1974; SR-26155-26157; Emerson, Lake & PalmerÂ â; Manticore (Box 44)
          MC 3-200 1298
        - Leonard Feather Presents The Sound Of Feeling, 1966; SR-26256; Feather, Leonard; Verve Records (Box 46)
          V6-8743; test pressing.
        - Fiddle-Faddle - Blue Tango - Sleigh Ride - 10 Other Leroy Anderson Favorites, 1962; SR-25911; Fiedler, Arthur; Boston Pops Orchestra, The; RCA Victor (Box 4)
          LSC-2638
        - Holiday for Strings, 1966; SR-25913; Fiedler, Arthur; Boston Pops Orchestra, The; RCA Victor (Box 4)
          LSC-2885
        - Rhapsody, 1964; SR-25912; Fiedler, Arthur; Boston Pops Orchestra, The; RCA Victor (Box 4)
          LSC-2746
        - Star Dust, 1963; SR-25910; Fiedler, Arthur; Boston Pops Orchestra, The; RCA Victor (Box 4)
          LSC-2670
        - Tchaikovsky: The Nutcracker (Excerpts), 1958; SR-25909; Fiedler, Arthur; Boston Pops Orchestra, The; RCA Victor (Box 4)
          LSC-2052
        - The Symphony: Great Moments in Music, 1980; SR-25908; Fiedler, Arthur; Boston Pops Orchestra, The; Time-Life Records (Box 4)
        - Trilogy for the Masses, 1968; SR-25915; Ford Theatre; ABC Records (Box 4)
          ABCS-658
        - Aloha From Tennessee Ernie Ford, 1967; SR-26104; Ford, Tennessee Ernie; Capitol Records (Box 19)
          T-2681
        - Greatest American Waltzes, 1963; SR-25916; Francis, Connie; MGM Records (Box 4)
          E-4145
        - Love Italian Style, 1967; SR-25919; Francis, Connie; MGM Records (Box 4)
          E-4448
        - Second Hand Love and Other Hits, 1962; SR-25917; Francis, Connie; MGM Records (Box 4)
          SE 4049
        - Sings Jewish Favorites, 1960; SR-25920; Francis, Connie; MGM Records (Box 4)
          E3869
        - Sings the All Time International Hits, 1965; SR-25918; Francis, Connie; MGM Records (Box 4)
          SE-4298
        - Maximal Minimal EP, 2000; SR-26190; Frantik Frank; Over Nite Music Research (Box 45)
          OVNT-001-EP
        - Music For Voices, Instruments & Electronic Sounds, 1968; SR-26241; Gaburo, Kenneth; Nonesuch Records (Box 46)
          H-71199
        - Music For Voices, Instruments & Electronic Sounds, 1968; SR-20804; Gaburo, Kenneth; Nonesuch Records (Box 71)
        - Electronics / Five Improvisations On Magnetic Tape, 1961; SR-25921; Gassmann, Remi; Sala, Oskar; Westminster (Box 4)
          XWN 18962
        - First Moog Quartet, 1970; SR-26182; Gershon Kingsley's First Moog Quartet; Audio Fidelity (Box 44)
          ASFD 6234
        - Highlights, Undated; SR-25922; Gilbert and Sullivan; London Savoyard Orchestra; Lukas, Nigel; Classica (Box 4)
          CLAS 105
        - Music Around The World For Lovers Only, 1966; SR-25923; Gleason, Jackie; Capitol Records (Box 4)
          SW 2471
        - Beyond The Sun: An Electronic Portrait Of Holst's The Planets, 1976; SR-25924; Gleeson, Patrick; Mercury (Box 4)
          SR180000
        - Honey, 1968; SR-25925; Goldsboro, Barry; United Artists Records (Box 4)
          UAS 6642
        - Like Children, 1974; SR-26200; Goodman, Jerry; Hammer, Jan; Nemperor Records (Box 45)
          NE 430
        - Like Children, 1974; SR-26205; Goodman, Jerry; Hammer, Jan; Nemperor Records (Box 45)
        - Sousa Forever!, 1961; SR-26079; Gould, Morton, and His Symphonic Band; RCA Victor Red Seal (Box 12)
          LSC-2569
        - Radio In Österreich - Österreich Im Radio, 1984; SR-26080; Grissemann, Ernst; Treiber, Alfred; ORF (Box 12)
          120 739
        - Soundcheck, 1976; SR-26209; Gulgowski, Wlodek; Polydor Records (Box 45)
          2379 110
        - The First Seven Days, 1975; SR-26208; Hammer, Jan; Nemperor Records (Box 45)
          NE 432
        - Crossings, 1972; SR-26402; Hancock, Herbie; Warner Bros. Records (Box 71)
          BS 2617
        - Crossings, 1972; SR-26403; Hancock, Herbie; Warner Bros. Records (Box 71)
        - An Evening With Herbie Hancock & Chick Corea In Concert, 1978; SR-25926; Hancock, Herbie; Corea, Chick; Columbia Records (Box 4)
          PC2 35663
        - The Sonosopher Retrospective, 1998; SR-31447; Hanson, Sten; Alga Marghen â (Box 46)
          plana-H 6vocson017
          Back cover signed by Sten Hanson
        - Bad Luck is All I Have, 1975; SR-26220; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 1675
        - Come on Down!, 1970; SR-26225; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 1554
        - Excursions, 1973; SR-26218-26219; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 2-311
        - Free Speech, 1970; SR-26404; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 71)
          SD 1573
        - How Can You Live Like That?, 1977; SR-26221; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 1698
        - I Need Some Money, 1975; SR-26164; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 44)
          SD 1669
        - I Need Some Money, 1975; SR-26165; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 44)
        - Is It In?, 1974; SR-26226; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 1649
        - Live at Newport, 1971; SR-26224; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 1595
        - Plug Me In, 1968; SR-25932; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 4)
          SD 1506
        - Plug Me In, 1968; SR-26405; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 71)
        - Sings the Blues, 1975; SR-25929; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 4)
          SD 1625
        - That is Why You're Overweight, 1976; SR-26222; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 45)
          SD 1683
        - The Reason Why I'm Talking S--T, 1976; SR-25930; Harris, Eddie; Atlantic Recording Corporation (Box 4)
          SD 18165
        - My Fair Lady, 1956; SR-26105; Harrison, Rex; Andrews, Julie; Columbia Records (Box 19)
          OL 5090
        - Switched on Buck, 1971; SR-26149; Haskell, Jeff; Capitol Records (Box 44)
          ST-679
        - Genuine Electric Latin Love Machine, 1969; SR-26147; Hayman, Richard; Command Records (Box 44)
          947S
        - Genuine Electric Latin Love Machine, 1969; SR-26254; Hayman, Richard; Command Records (Box 46)
        - Showpieces, 1971; SR-25927; Heifetz, Jascha; RCA (Box 4)
          LSC-3232